connectlinks.info 2015-11-27

# — Connect Links

Privacy Policy Statement  
This is the web site of HimalayaIT.

Our postal address is  
000 W End Ave 00  
New York NY 10000  
We can be reached via e-mail at admin@domainprivateregistrationinfo  
Telephone: 347-913-5920

We respect your interest in your privacy and as a result we have created   
this informational disclosure. 

We collect and use personal information for many purposes, including but   
not limited to, billing; product and service fulfillment; to better   
understand our customer needs; to provide a better website, products and   
services; to communicate with customers and potential customers regarding   
our products and services and third party products and services. 

Generally, your private information will only be disclosed to our owners,   
employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, partners, affiliates,   
attorneys, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers   
and agents, acting on our behalf or request. This general rule, and   
disclosures in specific situations, is more particularly described below. 

You must be at least 18 years old to access this website. We do not direct   
this website to persons under 18, nor do we knowingly collect any personal   
information from children under the age of thirteen. 

Information Collected by our ISP 

The hosting provider for this Internet site (as with any Internet site) has   
the ability to record various information, including domain name, pages   
accessed, date and time of access, web browser type and computer operating   
system, and referring information, and to disclose this information. This   
is most commonly done by providing access to raw server logs. For more   
information you should perform an Internet search on 'server logs' or 'raw   
server logs.' We may have access to our raw server logs and access reports   
prepared by our hosting provider. 

Financial Information for Billing Purposes 

We sell products and services. When sales are made financial information   
must be disclosed. This information can include any number of facts you are   
asked to provide, but most commonly includes your name, financial / credit   
card information, billing address, and email address. Generally, this   
purchase information will be provided by you to a third party payment   
processor and we do not receive your financial / credit card information. 

In the event we do receive financial / credit card information, we will not   
disclose it to anyone unless disclosure is required by law or a court   
order, or unless disclosure is required to address an issue implicated by   
the financial transaction. If you claim that your financial information   
was used to make a purchase you did not authorize, details about the   
financial transaction may be disclosed to law enforcement and anyone else   
we deem necessary to address the matter. 

Use of eMail Addresses and other Contact Information 

An important part of our services includes being able to provide   
information to you. As a result, you expressly consent to receiving   
communications from us via email, fax, telephone, mail, text, SMS, or any   
other delivery method, including to your cell phone. 

As a customer you are agreeing to receive information about the product or   
service you purchased. This may include, but is not limited to, information   
about product or service updates, new features, or information we believe   
you may find interesting. 

We may also send you information about other products and services our   
company offers. 

We will not sell, provide, or transfer you email address to others. 

We may allow advertising to our customers, or engage in joint ventures,   
which result in your receiving advertisements from selected third parties. 

Identification of Purchasers 

If you purchase one of our products or services, you authorize us to use   
your name and identification information in advertising or promotions. 

We also use personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not   
individually attributable to you) for business analysis, operational,   
marketing and other promotional purposes. 

Unless we provide access to a membership area, account, or provide an   
ability to have and change a username, password, email address, or other   
similar information, we do not have the capability to allow users to review   
and request changes their personal information. 

Cookies and Tracking 

Cookies may be used to keep track of referred affiliate commissions and to   
monitor access to our website. You consent to any future use of cookies   
for testing purposes and the use of cookies for publicly available data to   
gather statistics for the purpose of determining which search engines,   
referring sites, key words, etc., bring visitors to our website, which   
pages visitors are most interested in, what web browsers are used, etc.   
Various providers may be used for this purpose. The purpose is to obtain   
information that will help promote the website, make the website more   
interesting and useful to visitors, and to identify areas where improvement   
is needed. 

Our website does not respond to “do not track” requests from a web browser   
or other device, or other similar requests or procedures. 

Additionally, various third party information suppliers and other entities   
that provide information for this website, or for use by us, may use   
cookies. Examples include, but are not necessarily limited to billing   
providers, third party advertisers, and third party resources we promote. 

We may also allow third party advertisers to display ads on our website.   
We are not in a position to know if they collect identifiable information   
about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across   
different websites, so you should assume they do. In most web browsers you   
can choose not to accept cookies from third party sites or third-party   
cookies. 

Disclosure by Necessity 

Private information may be disclosed if required by a court order, statute,   
law, or regulation. 

Information is subject to disclosure to address a claim that you are   
violating the terms of any agreement pertaining to your use of your use   
this website or our products or services, or rights of any third party. 

Information is also subject to disclosure if we believe that disclosure is   
necessary to identify, contact or bring an action against someone who may   
be causing injury to or interfering (either intentionally or   
unintentionally) with our rights or property, your rights or property,   
other users of our website, products or services, or anyone else. 

As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or   
buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company, or   
be bought by another company. In such transactions, personal information   
may be one of the transferred assets. 

Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which we   
maintain facilities or conduct operations. By using our website, products   
and services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of   
your country. 

After your account becomes inactive your information may remain in our   
databases, computers, and archives, and cannot reasonably be expunged. 

Policy Changes 

These policies may be amended by us at any time and without notice, but   
will be posted at this page. 

You agree that your continued use of our websites, product or service after   
that date will constitute your consent and acceptance of the amendment. 

Effective Date: September 30, 2015
